Privacy Policy
==============

1\. An overview of data protection
----------------------------------

**General information**

The following information will provide you with an easy to navigate overview of what will happen with your personal data when you visit this website. The term “personal data” comprises all data that can be used to personally identify you. For detailed information about the subject matter of data protection, please consult our Data Protection Declaration, which we have included beneath this copy.

**Data recording on this website**

**Who is the responsible party for the recording of data on this website (i.e. the “controller”)?**

The data on this website is processed by the operator of the website, whose contact information is available under section “Information Required by Law” on this website.

**How do we record your data?**

We collect your data as a result of your sharing of your data with us. This may, for instance be information you enter into our contact form.

Other data shall be recorded by our IT systems automatically or after you consent to its recording during your website visit. This data comprises primarily technical information (e.g. web browser, operating system or time the site was accessed). This information is recorded automatically when you access this website.

**What are the purposes we use your data for?**

A portion of the information is generated to guarantee the error free provision of the website. Other data may be used to analyze your user patterns.

**What rights do you have as far as your information is concerned?**

You have the right to receive information about the source, recipients and purposes of your archived personal data at any time without having to pay a fee for such disclosures. You also have the right to demand that your data are rectified or eradicated. If you have consented to data processing, you have the option to revoke this consent at any time, which shall affect all future data processing. Moreover, you have the right to demand that the processing of your data be restricted under certain circumstances. Furthermore, you have the right to log a complaint with the competent supervising agency.

Please do not hesitate to contact us at any time under the address disclosed in section “Information Required by Law” on this website if you have questions about this or any other data protection related issues.

**Analysis tools and tools provided by third parties**

There is a possibility that your browsing patterns will be statistically analyzed when your visit this website. Such analyses are performed primarily with what we refer to as analysis programs.

For detailed information about these analysis programs please consult our Data Protection Declaration below.

2\. Hosting and Content Delivery Networks (CDN)
-----------------------------------------------

**External Hosting**

This website is hosted by an external service provider (host). Personal data collected on this website are stored on the servers of the host. These may include, but are not limited to, IP addresses, contact requests, metadata and communications, contract information, contact information, names, web page access, and other data generated through a web site.

The host is used for the purpose of fulfilling the contract with our potential and existing customers (Art. 6 para. 1 lit. b GDPR) and in the interest of secure, fast and efficient provision of our online services by a professional provider (Art. 6 para. 1 lit. f GDPR).

Our host will only process your data to the extent necessary to fulfil its performance obligations and to follow our instructions with respect to such data.

**Execution of a contract data processing agreement**

In order to guarantee processing in compliance with data protection regulations, we have concluded an order processing contract with our host.

3\. General information and mandatory information
-------------------------------------------------

**Data protection**

The operators of this website and its pages take the protection of your personal data very seriously. Hence, we handle your personal data as confidential information and in compliance with the statutory data protection regulations and this Data Protection Declaration.

Whenever you use this website, a variety of personal information will be collected. Personal data comprises data that can be used to personally identify you. This Data Protection Declaration explains which data we collect as well as the purposes we use this data for. It also explains how, and for which purpose the information is collected.

We herewith advise you that the transmission of data via the Internet (i.e. through e-mail communications) may be prone to security gaps. It is not possible to completely protect data against third party access.

**Information about the responsible party (referred to as the “controller” in the GDPR)**

The data processing controller on this website is:

**GET Sol 1 GmbH**  
Berliner Str. 65  
04129 Leipzig  
Germany

E-Mail: info@preisvergleich.de

The controller is the natural person or legal entity that single-handedly or jointly with others makes decisions as to the purposes of and resources for the processing of personal data (e.g. names, e-mail addresses, etc.).

**Data protection officer**

Kevin Peter  
Corinthstr. 19  
04157 Leipzig  
Germany

**Information on data transfer to the USA**

Our website uses, in particular, tools from companies based in the USA. When these tools are active, your personal information may be transferred to the US servers of these companies. We must point out that the USA is not a safe third country within the meaning of EU data protection law. US companies are required to release personal data to security authorities without you as the data subject being able to take legal action against this. The possibility cannot therefore be excluded that US authorities (e.g. secret services) may process, evaluate and permanently store your data on US servers for monitoring purposes. We have no influence over these processing activities.

**Revocation of your consent to the processing of data**

A wide range of data processing transactions are possible only subject to your express consent. You can also revoke at any time any consent you have already given us. This shall be without prejudice to the lawfulness of any data collection that occurred prior to your revocation.

**Right to object to the collection of data in special cases; right to object to direct advertising (Art. 21 GDPR)**

IN THE EVENT THAT DATA ARE PROCESSED ON THE BASIS OF ART. 6 SECT. 1 LIT. E OR F GDPR, YOU HAVE THE RIGHT TO AT ANY TIME OBJECT TO THE PROCESSING OF YOUR PERSONAL DATA BASED ON GROUNDS ARISING FROM YOUR UNIQUE SITUATION. THIS ALSO APPLIES TO ANY PROFILING BASED ON THESE PROVISIONS. TO DETERMINE THE LEGAL BASIS, ON WHICH ANY PROCESSING OF DATA IS BASED, PLEASE CONSULT THIS DATA PROTECTION DECLARATION. IF YOU LOG AN OBJECTION, WE WILL NO LONGER PROCESS YOUR AFFECTED PERSONAL DATA, UNLESS WE ARE IN A POSITION TO PRESENT COMPELLING PROTECTION WORTHY GROUNDS FOR THE PROCESSING OF YOUR DATA, THAT OUTWEIGH YOUR INTERESTS, RIGHTS AND FREEDOMS OR IF THE PURPOSE OF THE PROCESSING IS THE CLAIMING, EXERCISING OR DEFENCE OF LEGAL ENTITLEMENTS (OBJECTION PURSUANT TO ART. 21 SECT. 1 GDPR).

IF YOUR PERSONAL DATA IS BEING PROCESSED IN ORDER TO ENGAGE IN DIRECT ADVERTISING, YOU HAVE THE RIGHT TO AT ANY TIME OBJECT TO THE PROCESSING OF YOUR AFFECTED PERSONAL DATA FOR THE PURPOSES OF SUCH ADVERTISING. THIS ALSO APPLIES TO PROFILING TO THE EXTENT THAT IT IS AFFILIATED WITH SUCH DIRECT ADVERTISING. IF YOU OBJECT, YOUR PERSONAL DATA WILL SUBSEQUENTLY NO LONGER BE USED FOR DIRECT ADVERTISING PURPOSES (OBJECTION PURSUANT TO ART. 21 SECT. 2 GDPR).

**Right to log a complaint with the competent supervisory agency**

In the event of violations of the GDPR, data subjects are entitled to log a complaint with a supervisory agency, in particular in the member state where they usually maintain their domicile, place of work or at the place where the alleged violation occurred. The right to log a complaint is in effect regardless of any other administrative or court proceedings available as legal recourses.

**Right to data portability**

You have the right to demand that we hand over any data we automatically process on the basis of your consent or in order to fulfil a contract be handed over to you or a third party in a commonly used, machine readable format. If you should demand the direct transfer of the data to another controller, this will be done only if it is technically feasible.

**SSL and/or TLS encryption**

For security reasons and to protect the transmission of confidential content, such as purchase orders or inquiries you submit to us as the website operator, this website uses either an SSL or a TLS encryption program. You can recognize an encrypted connection by checking whether the address line of the browser switches from “http://” to “https://” and also by the appearance of the lock icon in the browser line.

If the SSL or TLS encryption is activated, data you transmit to us cannot be read by third parties.

**Information about, rectification and eradication of data**

Within the scope of the applicable statutory provisions, you have the right to at any time demand information about your archived personal data, their source and recipients as well as the purpose of the processing of your data. You may also have a right to have your data rectified or eradicated. If you have questions about this subject matter or any other questions about personal data, please do not hesitate to contact us at any time at the address provided in section “Information Required by Law.”

**Right to demand processing restrictions**

You have the right to demand the imposition of restrictions as far as the processing of your personal data is concerned. To do so, you may contact us at any time at the address provided in section “Information Required by Law.” The right to demand restriction of processing applies in the following cases:

* In the event that you should dispute the correctness of your data archived by us, we will usually need some time to verify this claim. During the time that this investigation is ongoing, you have the right to demand that we restrict the processing of your personal data.
* If the processing of your personal data was/is conducted in an unlawful manner, you have the option to demand the restriction of the processing of your data in lieu of demanding the eradication of this data.
* If we do not need your personal data any longer and you need it to exercise, defend or claim legal entitlements, you have the right to demand the restriction of the processing of your personal data instead of its eradication.
* If you have raised an objection pursuant to Art. 21 Sect. 1 GDPR, your rights and our rights will have to be weighed against each other. As long as it has not been determined whose interests prevail, you have the right to demand a restriction of the processing of your personal data.

If you have restricted the processing of your personal data, these data – with the exception of their archiving – may be processed only subject to your consent or to claim, exercise or defend legal entitlements or to protect the rights of other natural persons or legal entities or for important public interest reasons cited by the European Union or a member state of the EU.

4\. Recording of data on this website
-------------------------------------

**Cookies**

Our websites and pages use what the industry refers to as “cookies.” Cookies are small text files that do not cause any damage to your device. They are either stored temporarily for the duration of a session (session cookies) or they are permanently archived on your device (permanent cookies). Session cookies are automatically deleted once you terminate your visit. Permanent cookies remain archived on your device until you actively delete them or they are automatically eradicated by your web browser.

In some cases it is possible that third party cookies are stored on your device once you enter our site (third party cookies). These cookies enable you or us to take advantage of certain services offered by the third party (e.g. cookies for the processing of payment services).

Cookies have a variety of functions. Many cookies are technically essential since certain website functions would not work in the absence of the cookies (e.g. the shopping cart function or the display of videos). The purpose of other cookies may be the analysis of user patterns or the display of promotional messages.

Cookies, which are required for the performance of electronic communication transactions (required cookies) or for the provision of certain functions you want to use (functional cookies, e.g. for the shopping cart function) or those that are necessary for the optimization of the website (e.g. cookies that provide measurable insights into the web audience), shall be stored on the basis of Art. 6 Sect. 1 lit. f GDPR, unless a different legal basis is cited. The operator of the website has a legitimate interest in the storage of cookies to ensure the technically error free and optimized provision of the operator’s services. If your consent to the storage of the cookies has been requested, the respective cookies are stored exclusively on the basis of the consent obtained (Art. 6 Sect. 1 lit. a GDPR); this consent may be revoked at any time.

You have the option to set up your browser in such a manner that you will be notified any time cookies are placed and to permit the acceptance of cookies only in specific cases. You may also exclude the acceptance of cookies in certain cases or in general or activate the delete function for the automatic eradication of cookies when the browser closes. If cookies are deactivated, the functions of this website may be limited.

In the event that third party cookies are used or if cookies are used for analytical purposes, we will separately notify you in conjunction with this Data Protection Policy and, if applicable, ask for your consent.

**Server log files**

The provider of this website and its pages automatically collects and stores information in so-called server log files, which your browser communicates to us automatically. The information comprises:

* The type and version of browser used
* The used operating system
* Referrer URL
* The hostname of the accessing computer
* The time of the server inquiry
* The IP address

This data is not merged with other data sources.

This data is recorded on the basis of Art. 6 Sect. 1 lit. f GDPR. The operator of the website has a legitimate interest in the technically error free depiction and the optimization of the operator’s website. In order to achieve this, server log files must be recorded.

5\. Analysis tools and advertising
----------------------------------

**Google Analytics**

This website uses functions of the web analysis service Google Analytics. The provider of this service is Google Ireland Limited (“Google”), Gordon House, Barrow Street, Dublin 4, Ireland.

Google Analytics enables the website operator to analyze the behavior patterns of website visitors. To that end, the website operator receives a variety of user data, such as pages accessed, time spent on the page, the utilized operating system and the user’s origin. Google may consolidate these data in a profile that is allocated to the respective user or the user’s device.

Google Analytics uses technologies that make the recognition of the user for the purpose of analyzing the user behavior patterns (e.g. cookies or device fingerprinting). The website use information recorded by Google is, as a rule transferred to a Google server in the United States, where it is stored.

This analysis tool is used on the basis of Art. 6 Sect. 1 lit. f GDPR. The operator of this website has a legitimate interest in the analysis of user patterns to optimize both, the services offered online and the operator’s advertising activities. If a corresponding agreement has been requested (e.g. an agreement to the storage of cookies), the processing takes place exclusively on the basis of Art. 6 para. 1 lit. a GDPR; the agreement can be revoked at any time.

**IP anonymization**

On this website, we have activated the IP anonymization function. As a result, your IP address will be abbreviated by Google within the member states of the European Union or in other states that have ratified the Convention on the European Economic Area prior to its transmission to the United States. The full IP address will be transmitted to one of Google’s servers in the United States and abbreviated there only in exceptional cases. On behalf of the operator of this website, Google shall use this information to analyze your use of this website to generate reports on website activities and to render other services to the operator of this website that are related to the use of the website and the Internet. The IP address transmitted in conjunction with Google Analytics from your browser shall not be merged with other data in Google’s possession.

**Browser plug-in**

You can prevent the recording and processing of your data by Google by downloading and installing the browser plugin available under the following link: [https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en). 

For more information about the handling of user data by Google Analytics, please consult Google’s Data Privacy Declaration at: [https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245?hl=en](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245?hl=en).

**Demographic parameters provided by Google Analytics**

This website uses the “demographic characteristics” function of Google Analytics, to be able to display to the website visitor compatible ads within the Google advertising network. This allows reports to be created that contain information about the age, gender and interests of the website visitors. The sources of this information are interest-related advertising by Google as well as visitor data obtained from third party providers. This data cannot be allocated to a specific individual. You have the option to deactivate this function at any time by making pertinent settings changes for advertising in your Google account or you can generally prohibit the recording of your data by Google Analytics as explained in section “Objection to the recording of data”.

**Google Analytics E-Commerce-Tracking**

This website uses the “E-Commerce Tracking” function of Google Analytics. With the assistance of E-Commerce Tracking, the website operator is in a position to analyze the purchasing patterns of website visitors with the aim of improving the operator’s online marketing campaigns. In this context, information, such as the orders placed, the average order values, shipping costs and the time from viewing the product to making the purchasing decision are tracked. These data may be consolidated by Google under a transaction ID, which is allocated to the respective user or the user’s device.

**Archiving period**

Data on the user or incident level stored by Google linked to cookies, user IDs or advertising IDs (e.g. DoubleClick cookies, Android advertising ID) will be anonymized or deleted after 14 month. For details please click the following link: [https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/7667196?hl=es](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/7667196?hl=es)

**Google Ads**

The website operator uses Google Ads. Google Ads is an online promotional program of Google Ireland Limited (“Google”), Gordon House, Barrow Street, Dublin 4, Ireland.

Google Ads enables us to display ads in the Google search engine or on third party websites, if the user enters certain search terms into Google (keyword targeting). It is also possible to place targeted ads based on the user data Google has in its possession (e.g. location data and interests; target group targeting). As the website operator, we can analyze these data quantitatively, for instance by analyzing which search terms resulted in the display of our ads and how many ads led to respective clicks.

The use of Google Ads is based on Art. 6 Sect. 1 lit. et seq. GDPR. The website operator has a legitimate interest in marketing the operator’s services and products as effectively as possible.

**Google AdSense**

This website uses Google AdSense, a service for the integration of ads. The provider of this service is Google Ireland Limited (“Google”), Gordon House, Barrow Street, Dublin 4, Ireland.

With the assistance of Google Adsense we are in a position to place targeted ads by third parties on our site. The contents of the ads are based on your interests, which Google determines based on your past user patterns. Moreover, when choosing compatible ads, context information, such as your location, the content of the visited website or Google search terms you have entered, will be taken into account.

Google AdSense uses Cookies, Web Beacons (invisible graphics) and comparable recognition technologies. As a result, it is possible to analyze information, such as visitor traffic data, on these sites.

The usage information for this website (including your IP address) recorded by Google Adsense and delivery of advertising formats are transferred to a Google server in the United States, where the information is stored. Google may share this information with one of its contracting partners. However, Google will not link your IP address with any other of your stored information.

Our use of AdSense is based on Art. 6 Sect. 1 lit. et seq. GDPR. The website operator has a legitimate interest in the marketing of the operator’s website that is as effective as possible. If a respective declaration of consent was requested, processing shall occur exclusively on the basis of Art. 6 Sect. 1 lit. a GDPR; the given consent may be revoked at any time.

**Google Remarketing**

This website uses the functions of Google Analytics Remarketing. The provider of these solutions is Google Ireland Limited (“Google”), Gordon House, Barrow Street, Dublin 4, Ireland.

Google Remarketing analyzes your user patterns on our website (e.g. clicks on specific products), to allocate a certain advertising target groups to you and to subsequently display matching online offers to you when you visit other online offers (remarketing or retargeting).

Moreover, it is possible to link the advertising target groups generated with Google Remarketing to device encompassing functions of Google. This makes it possible to display interest-based customized advertising messages, depending on your prior usage and browsing patterns on a device (e.g. cell phone) in a manner tailored to you as well as on any of your devices (e.g. tablet or PC).

If you have a Google account, you have the option to object to personalized advertising under the following link: [https://adssettings.google.com/authenticated?hl=en](https://adssettings.google.com/authenticated?hl=en).

The use of Google Remarketing is based on Art. 6 1 lit. et seq. GDPR. The website operator has a legitimate interest in the marketing of the operator’s products that is as effective as possible. If a respective declaration of consent was requested, processing shall occur exclusively on the basis of Art. 6 Sect. 1 lit. a GDPR; the given consent may be revoked at any time.

For further information and the pertinent data protection regulations, please consult the Data Privacy Policies of Google at: [https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads?hl=es](https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads?hl=es).

**Formation of Target Groups with Customer Reconciliation**

For the formation of target groups, we use, among other things, the Google Remarketing customer reconciliation feature. To achieve this, we transfer certain customer data (e.g. email addresses) from our customer lists to Google. If the respective customers are Google users and are logged into their Google accounts, matching advertising messages within the Google network (e.g. YouTube, Gmail or in a search engine) are displayed for them to view.

**Google Conversion-Tracking**

This website uses Google Conversion Tracking. The provider of this service is Google Ireland Limited (“Google”), Gordon House, Barrow Street, Dublin 4, Ireland.

With the assistance of Google Conversion Tracking we are in a position to recognize whether the user has completed certain actions. For instance, we can analyze the how frequently which buttons on our website have been clicked and which products are reviewed or purchased with particular frequency. The purpose of this information is to compile conversion statistics. We learn how many users have clicked on our ads and which actions they have completed. We do not receive any information that would allow us to personally identify the users. Google as such uses cookies or comparable recognition technologies for identification purposes.

We use Google Conversion Tracking on the basis of Art. 6 Sect. 1 lit. et seq. GDPR. The operator of the website has a legitimate interest in the analysis of the user patterns with the aim of optimizing both, the operator’s web presentation and advertising. If a respective declaration of consent was requested (e.g. concerning the storage of cookies), processing shall occur exclusively on the basis of Art. 6 Sect. 1 lit. a GDPR; the given consent may be revoked at any time.

For more information about Google Conversion Tracking, please review Google’s data protection policy at: [https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en)

**Google DoubleClick**

This website uses features of Google DoubleClick. The provider is Google Ireland Limited (“Google”), Gordon House, Barrow Street, Dublin 4, Ireland, (hereinafter “DoubleClick”).

DoubleClick is used to show you interest-based ads across the Google Network. Advertisements can be tailored to the interests of the viewer using DoubleClick. For example, our ads may appear in Google search results or in banners associated with DoubleClick.

To be able to display interest adequate promotional content to users, DoubleClick must recognize the respective visitor so that it can allocate the websites visited, the clicks and other user pattern information to the user. To do this, DoubleClick deploys cookies or comparable recognition technologies (e.g. device fingerprinting). The recorded information is consolidated into a pseudonym user profile so that the respective user can be shown interest adequate advertising.

The use of Google DoubleClick takes place in the interest of targeted advertising measures. This constitutes a legitimate interest within the meaning of Art. 6 para. 1 lit. f GDPR. If a corresponding agreement has been requested (e.g. an agreement to the storage of cookies), the processing takes place exclusively on the basis of Art. 6 para. 1 lit. a GDPR; the agreement can be revoked at any time.

For further information on how to object to the advertisements displayed by Google, please see the following links: [https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads?hl=es](https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads?hl=es) and [https://adssettings.google.com/authenticated?hl=es](https://adssettings.google.com/authenticated?hl=es).

**Google Web Fonts**

This site uses so-called web fonts, which are provided by Google, for the uniform display of fonts. When you call up a page, your browser loads the required web fonts into its browser cache in order to display texts and fonts correctly. For this purpose, the browser you are using must connect to Google's servers. This enables Google to know that our website has been accessed via your IP address. The use of Google Web Fonts is in the interest of a uniform and attractive presentation of our online offers.

This represents a legitimate interest within the meaning of Art. 6 para. 1 lit. f GDPR. If your browser does not support Web Fonts, a standard font will be used by your computer. Further information on Google Web Fonts can be found at [https://developers.google.com/fonts/faq](https://developers.google.com/fonts/faq) and in the Google data protection declaration: [https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=es](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=es).

**Bing Conversion Tracking**

This website uses Google Conversion Tracking. The provider of this service is Microsoft Corporation, One Microsoft Way, Redmond, WA 98052-6399, USA.

With the assistance of Google Conversion Tracking we are in a position to recognize whether the user has completed certain actions. For instance, we can analyze the how frequently which buttons on our website have been clicked and which products are reviewed or purchased with particular frequency. The purpose of this information is to compile conversion statistics. We learn how many users have clicked on our ads and which actions they have completed. We do not receive any information that would allow us to personally identify the users. Google as such uses cookies or comparable recognition technologies for identification purposes.

We use Google Conversion Tracking on the basis of Art. 6 Sect. 1 lit. et seq. GDPR. The operator of the website has a legitimate interest in the analysis of the user patterns with the aim of optimizing both, the operator’s web presentation and advertising. If a respective declaration of consent was requested (e.g. concerning the storage of cookies), processing shall occur exclusively on the basis of Art. 6 Sect. 1 lit. a GDPR; the given consent may be revoked at any time.

You can deactivate Bing Ads anytime. Please follow the instructions on this website: [https://account.microsoft.com/privacy/ad-settings/signedout?lang=es-es](https://account.microsoft.com/privacy/ad-settings/signedout?lang=es-es)

**Kibana**

Our website uses Kibana to analyse users. Kibana is a proprietary tracking tool that we use to record what keywords a user searches for, what browser they use and what cookie ID a user has. The cookie-ID is used to uniquely recognise the user and to be able to connect user data. On the Internet, every device requires a unique address, the so-called IP address, to transmit data. Due to the way the Internet works, it is technically necessary to store the IP address at least temporarily.

The IP addresses are shortened by 1 byte before any processing and are only processed further in an anonymised form. There is no saving or further processing of the unabridged IP addresses. Tracking with Kibana is carried out with justified interest in accordance with Art. 6 Sect. 1 lit. et seq. GDPR. The purpose of the processing of personal data is the compilation of statistics. The statistics serve to be able to track and document the use of our offer.

**MarinOne Software**

MarinOne is a software by Marin Software, 123 Mission Street, 27th Floor, San Francisco, CA 94105, USA, which we use to optimize our search engine advertising. MarinOne uses so called “cookies”, text files which are stored on your computer allowing to analyse the usage of our website.

1. Purpose: Measuring the ad effectiveness through aggregating all users for a given ad and criterion (e.g. search term)
2. Collecting data: Through browser cookie
3. Storage period: 1-90 days, depending on the browser
4. Recipient of information: Marin Software
5. Processing region: IP addresses are obfuscated inside the EU, cookie processing within the USA
6. Legal basis: To be forgotten and/or prevent your data from being used, clear these cookies inside your browser.

For further questions please contact [privacy@marinsoftware.com](mailto:privacy@marinsoftware.com)

6\. Online marketing and partner programs
-----------------------------------------

**Amazon partner program**

The operators of this website participate in the Amazon EU partners’ program. Amazon integrates ads and links to the German Amazon website - Amazon.de - into this website, which allows us to generate earnings in the form of advertising cost reimbursements. Amazon uses cookies or comparable technologies for recognition (e.g. device-fingerprinting) for this program to be able to determine the source of orders placed. This allows Amazon to determine that you have clicked the partner link on this website.

Data are stored and analyzed on the basis of Art. 6 Sect. 1 lit. f GDPR. The website operator has a legitimate interest in the correct calculation of the operator’s affiliate compensation. If a respective declaration of consent has been obtained (e.g. consent to the archiving of cookies), the data will be processed exclusively on the basis of Art. 6 Sect. 1 lit. a DGDPR. Any such consent may be revoked at any time.

For more information on Amazon’s data usage, please consult Amazon’s Data Privacy Declaration under the following link:

[https://www.amazon.es/gp/help/customer/display.html/ref=hp\_left\_v4\_sib?ie=UTF8&nodeId=201909010](https://www.amazon.es/gp/help/customer/display.html/ref=hp_left_v4_sib?ie=UTF8&nodeId=201909010)

7\. Cookie Settings
-------------------

You can modify your cookie settings anytime here.

8\. Partners
------------

Some Partners help us with our marketing services, statistics and functionalities. This list provides a list of our partners and the cookies they use:

### Marketing

Bing Ads (“\_uetsid“, „NAP“, “ANON”, “MUIDB”, “TOptOut”, “MUID”)

Google Ads (“\_\_sonar”, “\_\_gads”, “\_gcl\_\*”, “1P\_JAR”, “IDE”, “\_\_Secure-HSID”, “DSID”, “\_\_ar\_v\*”, “ANID”, “SAPISID”, “DSID”, “id”, “\_sonar”, “CONSENT”, “CONSENT”, “SIDCC”, “\_\_Secure-3PSID”, “1P\_JAR”, “SSID”, “\_gads”, “SID”, “NID”, “APISID”, “HSID”, “\_\_Secure-3PAPISID”. “\_\_Secure-APISID”, “test\_cookie”, “\_\_gads”, “\_\_Secure-SSID”)

### Statistcis

Google Analytics (“\_gat\_UA-62476334-1”, “\_\_utmt”, “\_\_\_utmvc”, “\_gac\_”, “\_opt\_awgid”, “\_gaexp”, “\_\_utmb”, “\_opt\_awkid”, “GAPS”, “\_ga”, “\_opt\_awmid”, “\_opt\_utmc”, “\_\_utmz”, “\_\_utmx”, “\_\_utmxx”, “\_dc\_gtm\_\*”, “AMP\_TOKEN”, “\_\_utmt\_b”, “\_\_utmv”, “\_\_utmc”, “\_\_utmt\_a”, “\_gid”, “\_\_utma”, “\_opt\_awcid”)

### Functionalities

Google Tag Manager (“ht gtm\_debug“, „gtm\_internal“, „gtm\_auth“, „gtm\_preview“)

### Security and Privacy

Truendo Privacy Management (“truendo-tcf-v2”, “truendo\_\*”, “truendo-tcf-v2-glo<”)

Copyright 2024 by best-deal.com
